PRAYER FOR HEALING WITH PROPHET TB JOSHUA!!!
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are, whatever sickness,
I order all pain, all infection, to leave your body in the name of Jesus!
In your kidneys, in your blood, I order them to leave your body, in the name of Jesus!
In your kidneys, in your blood, in your muscles, in your bones, out!
Are you on the sickbed?
Whatever name they call your sickness, never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
I order that sickness, I order that disease.
I say, I command that disease to leave your body,
to leave your bones, to leave your blood, to leave your muscles, to leave your kidneys,
to leave your bones, to leave your flesh, in the name of Jesus!
Where can they hide?
Your body is a temple of the Holy Ghost. Where can disease hide?
My body is a temple of the Holy Ghost!
Your body is a temple of the Holy Ghost. Where can they hide?
Every hidden pain, every hidden disease, every hidden sickness, I command them out in the name of Jesus!
I command them out in the name of Jesus!
Out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
Viewers, my body is a temple of the Holy Ghost. Your body is a temple of the Holy Ghost.
Where can sickness hide? Where can disease hide?
Where can affliction hide?
Where can infection hide?
Holy Ghost!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here, to subscribe, to witness more of God's power and work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with our latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.